http://www.sportsjobboard.com/pages/privacy-policy

Privacy Policy
This Privacy Policy describes the how Sports Job Board collects, uses and discloses the Personal Information we collect about our users, including jobseekers, employers and guests when you use Sports Job Board website or mobile application and the services available through each. By using Sports Job Board you consent to the information collection and use practices described in this Privacy Policy. Your use of Sports Job Board, and any dispute over privacy, is subject to this Privacy Policy and our Terms of Use, including its applicable limitations on damages and the resolution of disputes. Please read this Privacy Policy to learn more about the ways in which we collect, use and protect your Personal Information. If you have questions or complaints regarding our privacy policy or practices, please contact us at privacy@SportsJobBoard.com For the purposes of this Privacy Policy, "Personal Information" means information that would allow a third party to learn your identity or contact you, including, for example, your full name, address, telephone number, email address, or credit card number. Your privacy is important to us. Our goal is to earn and keep your trust, according to the following principles:We will never rent or sell your personal information to third parties for marketing purposesWe will never share your contact information with a recruiter or hiring manager, unless both of you choose to contact one another regarding an open positionAny sensitive information that you provide will be secured with all industry standard protocols and technologyWhen this Privacy Policy uses the term "personally identifiable information" or "personal information," we mean information that identifies a particular individual, such as your full name, street address or email address. When other information, such as your target job category, is associated with personal information, it also becomes personally identifiable information for the purposes of this privacy policy. Please read this Privacy Policy to learn more about the ways in which we use and protect your personal information. Resume Should you post your resume, the amount of information you choose to keep confidential is entirely up to your discretion. You may enter as much or as little information as you choose. All information posted will only be visible to recruiters and companies seeking employees. All recruiters are screened and have been determined by Sports Job Board to be legitimately seeking applicants for open positions. Service Providers We use third parties to provide credit card processing services on our site. If you purchase service, we will share your personal information with this service provider to bill you for the services purchased. This service provider will only use your information to provide the services requested and will not use your information for any other purpose including their own marketing. This process is highly secure. Log Files Like many websites, we use and maintain the information that we obtain from your browser on our server logs. This information can include Internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, Internet service provider ("ISP"), and other data. We may use this information to analyze trends, administer the Site, track user movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. We may associate this information with your Personal Information to resolve technical issues and support security for our users. Changes to this Web Site Privacy Statement If we decide to change this Web Site Privacy Statement, we will post the revised policy at this location, or at another location that is accessible via link from our homepages, so that users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under circumstances, if any, we disclose it. If at any point we decide to use Personal Information in a manner that is substantially different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will seek to notify users by way of an email, and provide users with a choice as to whether or not we use their information in this different manner. Our Sites are not intended for children under 18 years of age. We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under 18. If you have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us at: Sports Job Board, 73211 Foxtail Lane, Suite D, Palm Desert, CA 92260 Tel: (760)469-2119
